Yes, sir. This is John Spikes taking Las
Vegas. How you doing?
I'm doing good. You still got that
silver and black
outfit you showed me?
>> Hell yeah, you spoke it into existence,
man. Yes, sir.
I appreciate you. Yeah, I appreciate
you, man. You need to bring that energy
and that
that growth mindset that you got, right?
Always getting better. You're still
sending
Enjoy the time with your family and
welcome to the dark side. How you doing?
Yes, sir.
I'm good, coach. I'm blessed. Welcome to
the silver and black. You did a great
>> to ride We going to rock the hell out. I
promise. Make sure you keep improving
when you get here. You got me? Listen, I
got you.
All right, hey. I want to talk to
Robbie, our defensive coordinator,
Robbie Leonard. Here you go. Let's do
it. Let's do it. Let's do it. You ready,
young man?
Hell yeah. Hey, hey,
pass rushers, man. You came to the right
spot. Tell you that.
>> Hey, I'm coming to study and learn and
work. You are? That's all you got to do.
You just work, you're going to be
straight. You with me? Let's do it.
Let's do it. Fired up. You going to do a
great room, man. Great room. You just
got to be ready to learn and work your
stuff, all right? I got you, coach. I
got you, coach.
I got you, coach.
Go enjoy this moment, brother. Talk to
you later.
With the 67th pick in the 2026 NFL
Draft,
the Raiders
select
Keiron Crawford, defensive end, Auburn.
>> [screaming]
[screaming]